Guide to the Richard Marshall Collection of Gay Erotica and Pornography MSS.498
Fales Library and Special Collections
Richard Marshall Collection of Gay Erotica and Pornography
1950-2011
Fales Library and Special Collections
Marshall, Richard, 1947-2014
Georgis, William T., 1958-
MSS.498
38 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes, 34 record cartons, and 1 flat box.
173 videocassettes (vhs)
120 videodiscs (dvd)
4 electronic discs (cd-rom)
New York-based curator, art consultant, and art historian Richard D. Marshall (1947-2014) worked for 20 years at the Whitney Museum, served as art editor of the Paris Review, and was curator at the Lever House Art Collection in New York. This collection contains erotic pulp novels; gay erotic and pornographic magazines, zines, serials, and internet fiction stories; widely-themed calendars and catalogs; gay erotic and pornographic illustrations; and pornographic films in VHS and DVD format from the 1980s to the early 2000s. Collectible dolls and other related items can also be found in this collection.
Arrangement
This collection was kept in the creator's original arrangement, grouped by item type. Within these groupings, items were arranged and series were made by Fales student workers. This collection is divided into twelve series, three of which have been separated further into subseries. The series and subseries in the collection are as follows:
Series I. Pulp Novels, 1972-1996, undated
Series II. Magazines and Serials, 1948-2011, undated
Subseries II.A. Magazines, 1948-2011, undated
Subseries II.B. Serials, 1981-2000
Series III. Zines, 1964-2009, undated
Series IV. Pornographic Film Tie-ins, 1977-1983, undated
Series V. Catalogs and Calendars, 1997-2006, undated
Series VI. Advertisements, 1998-2000, undated
Series VII. Graphics, 1950-2007, undated
Subseries VII.A. Graphics and Illustrations, 1998-2000, undated
Subseries VII.B. Japanese Publications, 1950-2007, undated
Series VIII. Web Fiction, 1986-2003, undated
Series IX. Films, 1981-2007, undated
Subseries IX.A. Videocassettes (VHS), 1981-2004, undated
Subseries IX.B. Videodiscs (DVD), 1995-2007, undated
Series X. Clippings, 1997-2010, undated
Series XI. Dolls and Objects, 2003-2009, undated
Series XII. Work Files, 1964-2008, undated
Biographical Note
New York-based curator, art consultant, and art historian Richard D. Marshall (1947-2014) worked for 20 years at the Whitney Museum, where he organized numerous Biennial Exhibitions of contemporary art, and many seminal one-artist and group exhibitions. He served as art editor of the Paris Review, from 1975-1990 and was also curator for more than a decade at the Lever House Art Collection in New York beginning in 2003. He passed away in California in 2014 at the age of 67.
Sources:
http://www.artnews.com/2014/08/14/richard-d-marshall-longtime-whitney-curator-who-helped-build-the-lever-house-collection-dies-at-67/
http://www.legacy.com/obituaries/nytimes/obituary.aspx?pid=172073310
Conditions Governing Access
Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections.
Audiovisual material in this collection is not available for playback. Researchers may view an item's original container.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by William T. Georgis in 2016. The accession number associated with this gift is 2017.088.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains erotic pulp novels from the 1970s to the 1990s; gay erotic and pornographic magazines, zines, and serials spanning the 1940s through 2011; themed calendars and catalogs; gay erotic and pornographic illustrations; pornographic internet fiction stories written during the 1980s through the 2000s; and pornographic films in VHS and DVD format from the 1980s to the early 2000s. Tom of Finland "001 Rebel" and "Carlos the First Out and Proud Boyfriend" collectible dolls, as well as other related items can also be found in this collection. This collection illustrates the accumulation of pornography and erotic material by a gay man with a wide range of sexual interests, while living in New York during the 1970s through the 2000s. Additionally these same materials were used by Marshall as research and content for his proposed book illustrating homoerotic art throughout history. This collection includes a mock-up of the proposed book with supporting material.
Custodial History
The material was kept in Marshall's office apartment on the Upper East Side of New York until it was boxed up by his heirs and donated to Fales in 2016.
Separated Materials
Issues of G-Men, the Japanese manga magazine, were separated from this collection and catalogued individually.
The following items were deaccessioned by the Librarian for Fales Archival Collection and Reference:
Red velvet purse with 8.5 in glass dildo
T-Shirt. White, with black printed drawing of a naked man with six arms and a snake penis
Tom of Finland Doll
Red rubber double-ended dildo. In plastic wrap. (17 inches)
Black Anal Plug (11 inches)
RealCast Kris Lord Supercock. 'Lifesize' dildo in red draw-string bag (10 inches)
Gay pornographic films.; manga (comic books); VHS; DVDs.; Paperbacks.; Gay men -- Sexual behavior -- United States; Gay erotic stories, American; Magazines (Periodicals); Gay erotic literature.; Georgis, William T., 1958-
- Series I. Pulp Novels, 1972-1996, undated; 5 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains gay male-themed erotic pulp novels written around the 1970s to the 1990s.
  Arrangement
  The novels are arranged alphabetically by publisher, then numerically by publisher code.
  - Maston, Raymond. Hard Hat Boss. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. September 1983. Gay 104., cuid23238 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Sambar, David. Big Rig Hunks. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. August 1984. Gay 123., cuid23239 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dayton, Lester. Hunk Jumpers. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. December 1984. Gay 127., cuid23240 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Hayes, Adam. Big Rig. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. 1985. DS 168., cuid23241 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Todd, Allen. Hunky Brothers. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. 1983. MP 102., cuid23242 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fields, Bruce. Slave to Pleasure. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. 1983. MP 103., cuid23243 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Howard, Carlton. Hang up Hunk. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. 1983. MP 113., cuid23244 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Fields, Bruce. Full Throat. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. 1984. MP 123., cuid23245 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Romen, Stuart. Hard at Work. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. 1984. MP 125., cuid23246 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fields, Bruce. Dark and Dangerous. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. 1984. MP 126., cuid23247 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Carter, Matt. Peter Powerful. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. 1984. MP 131., cuid23248 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Robertson, Pete. Cocky Crew. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. 1984. MP 132., cuid23249 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Robertson, Pete. Meat Master. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. 1985. MP 137., cuid23250 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ward, Michael. Ballsy Biker. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. 1985. MP 140., cuid23251 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Peters, Andy. Fill 'em Up. North Hollywood California. Arena Publications. 1986. MP 163., cuid23252 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Levy, Martin. Just Following Orders, Sir! Wilmington, Delaware. Eros Publishing Company. 1982. GYP 108., cuid23253 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Love, F.W. Dorm Buddies. San Diego, California. Greenleaf Classics, Inc. 1976. AC 133., cuid23254 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lewis, Barton. Suckers for Truckers. San Diego, California. Greenleaf Classics, Inc. 1981. AC 251., cuid23255 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Stevens, Warren. Weekend Cruising. San Diego, California. Greenleaf Classics, Inc. 1981. AC 259., cuid23256 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bonds, Jason. Sins of the Father. San Diego, California. Greenleaf Classics, Inc. 1983. AC 294., cuid23257 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lewis, Barton. Hollywood Marine. San Diego, California. Greenleaf Classics, Inc.1983. AC 295., cuid23258 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dunn, Barry. Honor thy Father's Flesh. San Diego, California. Greenleaf Classics, Inc. 1984. AC 320, cuid23259 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dunn, Barry. Oh, Dad! More, Dad! San Diego, California. Greenleaf Classics, Inc. 1984. AC 321., cuid23260 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dunn, Barry. A Cop Coming Out. San Diego, California. Greenleaf Classics, Inc. 1984. AC 329., cuid23261 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dunn, Barry. A Cop Coming Out. San Diego, California. Greenleaf Classics, Inc. 1984. AC 329., cuid23262 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cranston, Wes. Schoolboy Into B & D. San Diego, California. Greenleaf Classics, Inc. 1984. AC 333., cuid23263 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cranston, Wes. Daddy's Buggerboy. San Diego, California. Greenleaf Classics, Inc. 1985. AC 340., cuid23264 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Marsh, Franklin D. Scat Slavers. San Diego, California. Greenleaf Classics, Inc. 1985. AC 347., cuid23265 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Ross, Johnny. Hot Chicken: Take One. San Diego, California. Greenleaf Classics, Inc. 1985. AC 352., cuid23266 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - McCall, John. Daddy's Boy. Cleveland, Ohio. Magcorp Publishing Company, Inc. 1983. RB 101., cuid23267 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - McCall, Jack. Hard Connection. Cleveland, Ohio. Magcorp Publishing Company, Inc. 1984. RB 109., cuid23268 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - McCall, Jack. Ramrod. Cleveland, Ohio. Magcorp Publishing Company, Inc. 1984. RB 116., cuid23269 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - McCall, John. Big Daddy. Cleveland, Ohio. Magcorp Publishing Company, Inc. 1984. RB 122., cuid23270 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Caldwell, Clay. Tailpipe Trucker. New York, New York. Masquerade Books, Inc. 1975. 296-5., cuid23271 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Morgan, Christopher. The Sportsmen. New York, New York. Masquerade Books, Inc. 1996. 385-6., cuid23272 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Anfuss, C.K. The Cocky Cowboy. Rough Trade. RT 414., Undated; cuid23273 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Darren, Jason. Trucking Sucker. Rough Trade. RT 439., Undated; cuid23274 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Wilson, George. Sucked-In Sailor. Rough Trade. RT 442., Undated; cuid23275 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Newman, Alan. Glory Hole. Rough Trade. RT 452., Undated; cuid23276 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Hall, Mannie. Brownout Bait. Rough Trade. RT 459., Undated; cuid23277 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Luger, Kurt. Berlin Bullies. Rough Trade. 1978. RT 466., cuid23278 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Cummings, Spike. His Superior Officer. Rough Trade. RT 467., Undated; cuid23279 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Heller, Jess. Trucker's Load. Rough Trade. 1979. RT 474., cuid23280 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Unknown Author. Booted Master. Rough Trade. 1980. RT 486., cuid23281 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Unknown Author. Cowpoke. Rough Trade. 1980. RT 490., cuid23282 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Unknown Author. Hard Hat Dude. Rough Trade. 1981. RT 496., cuid23283 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Unknown Author. Hard Hat Dude. Rough Trade. 1981. RT 496., cuid23284 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Unknown Author. Big-Tooled Mechanic. Rough Trade. 1981. RT 498., cuid23285 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Unknown Author. Big-Tooled Mechanic. Rough Trade. 1981. RT 498., cuid23286 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Unknown Author. Big Rig Rapist. Rough Trade. 1981. RT 501, cuid23287 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Beck, Martin. Hardhat Hellers. Rough Trade. 1982. RT 505., cuid23288 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Raji, Mohammad. Truck Stop Torment. Rough Trade.1982. RT 506., cuid23289 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Unknown Author. Sailor's Liberty. Rough Trade.1982. RT 511., cuid23290 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Unknown Author. Leather Knights. Rough Trade. 1982. RT 512., cuid23291 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Unknown Author. Leather Knights. Rough Trade. 1982. RT 512., cuid23292 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Unknown Author. Boot Camp Recruit. Rough Trade. 1982. RT 522., cuid23293 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Unknown Author. Boot Camp Recruit. Rough Trade. 1982. RT 522., cuid23294 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Unknown Author. Brute Woodsman. Rough Trade. 1982. RT 524., cuid23295 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Unknown Author. Brute Woodsman. Rough Trade. 1982. RT 524., cuid23296 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Unknown Author. Hard Hat's Little Helper. Rough Trade. 1983. RT 525., cuid23297 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Unknown Author. Hard Hat's Little Helper. Rough Trade. 1983. RT 525., cuid23298 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Unknown Author. Rodeo Stud. Rough Trade.1983. RT 526., cuid23299 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Unknown Author. Biker Blitz. Rough Trade. 1983. RT 527., cuid23300 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Unknown Author. Top Kick. Rough Trade. 1983. RT 528., cuid23301 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Unknown Author. Biker Stud. Rough Trade.1983. RT 529, cuid23302 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Unknown Author. Biker Stud. Rough Trade.1983. RT 530, cuid23303 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Unknown Author. Oil Rig Ramrod. Rough Trade.1983. RT 533., cuid23304 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Unknown Author. Stud Father. Rough Trade. 1983. RT 536., cuid23305 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Unknown Author. Stud Father. Rough Trade.1983. RT 536., cuid23306 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Unknown Author. Grease Monkey. Rough Trade.1983. RT 538., cuid23307 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Unknown Author. Black Boy's Training. Rough Trade. 1984. RT 543., cuid23308 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Unknown Author. Black Boy's Training. Rough Trade. 1984. RT 543., cuid23309 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Unknown Author. Father & Son. Rough Trade.1984. RT 545., cuid23310 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Unknown Author. Black Marine D.I. Rough Trade. 1984. RT 547., cuid23311 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Unknown Author. Apprentice Trucker. Rough Trade. 1984. RT 548., cuid23312 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Unknown Author. Hard Time. Rough Trade. 1984. RT 555., cuid23313 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Unknown Author. Stock Car Stud. Rough Trade. 1984. RT 558., cuid23314 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Unknown Author. Hot Hose Firehouse. Rough Trade. 1985. RT 567., cuid23315 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Unknown Author. Steel Mill Stud. Rough Trade. 1985. RT 568., cuid23316 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Unknown Author. Hard Hat Hard-Ons. Rough Trade. 1985. RT 569., cuid23317 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Unknown Author. Wrangler Roper. Rough Trade. 1985. RT 571., cuid23318 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Unknown Author. Wrangler Roper. Rough Trade. 1985. RT 571., cuid23319 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Unknown Author. D.I.'s Big Stick. Rough Trade. 1985. RT 574., cuid23320 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Unknown Author. Hard Dirty Truckers. Rough Trade. 1986. RT 578., cuid23321 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Unknown Author. Hard Dirty Truckers. Rough Trade. 1986. RT 578., cuid23322 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Unknown Author. Mean Sailor's Toy. Rough Trade. 1986. RT 580., cuid23323 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Unknown Author. Forced To Take It. Rough Trade. 1986. RT 586., cuid23324 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Unknown Author. Roped Chicken. Rough Trade. 1986. RT 588., cuid23325 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Unknown Author. Gutter Boy. Rough Trade. 1986. RT 589., cuid23326 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Unknown Author. Sea Meat. Rough Trade. 1986. RT 590., cuid23327 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Unknown Author. Trucker's Trick. Rough Trade. 1986. RT 591., cuid23328 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Unknown Author. Trucker's Trick. Rough Trade. 1986. RT 591., cuid23329 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Unknown Author. Trucker Fuckers. Rough Trade. 1986. RT 594., cuid23330 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Unknown Author. Hard Action Chicken. Rough Trade. 1986. RT 596., cuid23331 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Unknown Author. Bunkhouse Punk. Rough Trade. 1986. RT 599., cuid23332 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Unknown Author. Trucker's Load. Rough Trade. 1979. RT 612., cuid23333 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Unknown Author. Men of Steel. Rough Trade. 1988. RT 614., cuid23334 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Von Hoss, Bruno. Summer Heat. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1989. BA 103., cuid23335 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Author Unknown. Beach Bum. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1980. FIN 5, cuid23336 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Author Unknown. Hard Ball. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1980. FIN 15., cuid23337 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Author Unknown. Rodeo Raunch Boy. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1985. FIN 98., cuid23338 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Author Unknown. Chicken on a Spit. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1985. FIN 100., cuid23339 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Author Unknown. Gas Jockey. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1981. FIN 136., cuid23340 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Terepka, Gilbert. Boy Master. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1988. FIN 149., cuid23341 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Author Unknown. Dynamite Guy. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1989. FIN 161., cuid23342 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Author Unknown. Dynamite Guy. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1989. FIN 161., cuid23343 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Author Unknown. Trucker Stud. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1979. FIN 172., cuid23344 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Author Unknown. Hot-assed Coach. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1985. FIN 184., cuid23345 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Author Unknown. Wild Stud. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1991. FIN 191., cuid23346 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Author Unknown. Engine Boys. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1991. FIN 195., cuid23347 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Author Unknown. Engine Boys. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1991. FIN 195., cuid23348 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Author Unknown. Uncle Jack's Funhouse. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1988. GI 126., cuid23349 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Petersen, Brian. Father Takes a Son. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1988. GI 138., cuid23350 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Author Unknown. My Father, My Favorite. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1989. GI 143., cuid23351 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Author Unknown. Hooked on Dad. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1989. GI 145., cuid23352 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Author Unknown. Hooked on Dad. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1989. GI 145., cuid23353 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Author Unknown. Bootlicker. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1979. GI 148., cuid23354 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Author Unknown. Boss Con. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1981. GI 156., cuid23355 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Author Unknown. Working the Docks. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1988. HT 102., cuid23356 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Author Unknown. Military Stud. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1979. NM 4., cuid23357 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Author Unknown. Tight End. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1980. NM 11., cuid23358 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Author Unknown. Boss Trucker. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1983. NM 69., cuid23359 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Author Unknown. Trucker Studs. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1985. NM 97., cuid23360 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Author Unknown. Hot Assed Coach. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1985. NM 111., cuid23361 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Author Unknown. Foreman's Fury. New York, New York. Star Distributors.1981. NM 131., cuid23362 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Author Unknown. Hot Trucker. New York, New York. Star Distributors. 1980. NM 164., cuid23363 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Author Unknown. Big Shot. New York, New York. Star Distributors.1989. NM 175., cuid23364 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Author Unknown. Big Shot. New York, New York. Star Distributors.1989. NM 175., cuid23365 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Author Unknown. Big Shot. New York, New York. Star Distributors.1989. NM 175., cuid23366 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Marshall, Jeff. Cock-Hungry Cowboy. New York, New York. Star Distributors.1977. SS 1013, cuid23367 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Cunningham, Bernard. Cruising the Main. New York, New York. Star Distributors.1988. YS 110., cuid23368 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Thomas, Len. Hard-Ass Hardhat. Santee, California. Surree Limited, Inc. 1975. HIS69145., cuid23369 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Unknown Author. Leather Sucker. Santee, California. Surree Limited, Inc. 1980. HIS69411., cuid23370 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Hancock, Bob. Dad's Hunky Lads. Santee, California. Surree Limited, Inc. 1980. HIS69424., cuid23371 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Ward, Michael. Randy Pants. Santee, California. Surree Limited, Inc. 1981. HIS69432., cuid23372 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Hancock, Bob. Trucker's Stud Sailor. Santee, California. Surree Limited Inc. 1975. SS 008, cuid23373 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Hancock, Bob. Trucker's Stud Son. Santee, California. Surree Limited Inc. 1975. SS 011, cuid23374 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Jennings, Newt. Gay Cruiser, Book 1. Santee, California. Surree Limited Inc. 1976. SS 019., cuid23375 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Hancock, Bob. Sailor's Hunky Trucker. Santee, California. Surree Limited Inc. 1976. SS 021., cuid23376 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Ward, Mike. Hot Young Houseboy. Santee, California. Surree Limited Inc. 1976. SS 022., cuid23377 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Grissom, David E. High-Ball Trucker. Santee, California. Surree Limited Inc. 1976. SS 023, cuid23378 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Grissom, David E. Asstrucker. Santee, California. Surree Limited Inc. 1976. SS 024., cuid23379 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Rowen, Stuart. Butch Bi-Trucker. Santee, California. Surree Limited Inc. 1976. SS 028., cuid23380 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pepper, Peter. Hot for Peter. Santee, California. Surree Limited Inc. 1976. SS 029., cuid23381 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Pepper, Peter. Hot for Peter. Santee, California. Surree Limited Inc. 1976. SS 029., cuid23382 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Michaels, Ward. Horny for Hardhats. Santee, California. Surree Limited Inc. 1976. SS 031., cuid23383 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Riggles, Jon. Big Bad Boss. Surree Limited Inc. 1981. SS 107., cuid23384 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Gronowski, Paul. Desert Trek Tricks. Surree Limited Inc. 1981. SS 108., cuid23385 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Riggles, Jon. Trapped & Tied. Surree Limited Inc. 1981. SS 112., cuid23386 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Caldwell, Clay. Humpin' Hayloft Cousins. Santee, California. Surey Books. 1981. HIS 69440., cuid23387 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Hancock, Bob. Horse-Hung Trucker. Santee, California. Surey Books. 1982. HIS 69456., cuid23388 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Benton, Josh. Bath House Pickup. Santee, California. Surey Books. 1983. HIS 69464., cuid23389 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Ward, Michael. Randy Studs. Santee, California. Surey Books. 1984. HIS 69477., cuid23390 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Herman, Chuck. Biker Boys. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1972. Gay 143., cuid23391 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Caldwell, Clay. Truckin' Naked. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1972. Gay 145., cuid23392 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Cochran, Bob. Flood Cumin'. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1973. Gay 170., cuid23393 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Patterson, Art. Trucker Sucker. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1974. Gay 185., cuid23394 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Pepper, Peter. Big Red Waggin'. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1974. Gay 198., cuid23395 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Rammer, Rod. Cockpit Cruiser. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1973. HIS 6974., cuid23396 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - McCandless, Chance. Rock Hard. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1974. HIS 6991., cuid23397 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Charles, Saxby L. Daddy's Chicken. Santee, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1976. HIS 69177., cuid23398 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Hancock, Bob. Truckstop Hunk. Santee, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1976. HIS 69180., cuid23399 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Hancock, Bob. Trucker Comin'. Santee, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1976. HIS 69184., cuid23400 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Van Damn, Dirk. Truck Driving Stud. 1985. HIS 69503., cuid23401 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Michael, Jay. Hot Dean, Hung Hunk. 1985. HIS 69514., cuid23402 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Frank, Edmund. Doing Daddy. 1986. HIS 69540., cuid23403 (Box 5, Folder 1)